<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</title>
    <link>https://www.yatan.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</description>
    <image>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</title>
      <url>https://www.yatan.co/images/yatan-logomjsmtr.webp</url>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/images/yatan-logomjsmtr.webp</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.yatan.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An old story about a Chinese Farmer</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/posts/chinesefarmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:38:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/posts/chinesefarmer/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Farmer Story </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin Assisted Therapy Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:38:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>Overview of how assisted therapy works Pre-treatment preparation: Patients undergo an extensive screening process to determine their eligibility for psilocybin-assisted therapy. They receive preparatory sessions to educate them about the treatment, manage expectations, and establish rapport with the therapist.
Psilocybin administration: During the psilocybin session, patients are given a single dose of psilocybin in a controlled, supportive environment with trained therapists present. The dose is typically administered orally, either in capsules or mixed with a liquid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Ode to the Mountain and the Bench</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/posts/an-ode-to-the-mountain-and-the-bench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/posts/an-ode-to-the-mountain-and-the-bench/</guid>
      <description>Guide to emoji usage in Hugo and DoIt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The unarguable checkin</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/checkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/checkin/</guid>
      <description>Every person has their own perspective which can very often be arguable. Your own experience is personal to each and thus unarguable, nobody can tell you what you sense, feel or think. Which is why we love this checkin so much inspired by the conscious leadership methodology. The unarguable checkin.
Your Sensory Experiences Outer sense: taste smell touch sound vision inner sense internal energetic sensations Your emotional experience joy anger sadness sexual / creative energy fear The occurence of your thoughts pictures sounds questions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Resilience</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/adaptive-resilience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/adaptive-resilience/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Resilience Practical tools to work more skillfully with difficult emotions, uncertainty and change, leading to increased team performance and well-being Bring Adaptive Resilience to your organization
Adaptive resilience is the ability to recover from adversity, adapt and thrive. It builds the capacity to be productive, resourceful, and creative while dealing with changing circumstances or adversity.
This interactive program uses a mindfulness-based approach to build the behaviors, mental habits, and practices that promote personal resilience while growing a culture of resilience within teams and organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Resilience</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/emotional-intelligence/adaptive-resilience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/emotional-intelligence/adaptive-resilience/</guid>
      <description>Practical tools to work more skillfully with difficult emotions, uncertainty and change, leading to increased team performance and well-being Bring Adaptive Resilience to your organization
Adaptive resilience is the ability to recover from adversity, adapt and thrive. It builds the capacity to be productive, resourceful, and creative while dealing with changing circumstances or adversity.
This interactive program uses a mindfulness-based approach to build the behaviors, mental habits, and practices that promote personal resilience while growing a culture of resilience within teams and organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death and Rebirth</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/deathandrebirth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 13:04:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/deathandrebirth/</guid>
      <description>Awakening the limitless potential of your mind, achieving all peace and happiness Death and Rebirth Required Reading You can download this text in PDF version English Version and Spanish Version.
Further required reading includes the following texts: The Wish-Fulfilling Golden Sun, by Lama Zopa Rinpoche (pp. 50–9)
Liberation in the Palm of Your Hand, , 1997 gold edition (pp. 332–93 ) or 2006 blue edition (pp. 294- 321)
Advice on Dying and Living a Better Life, by His Holiness the Dalai Lama</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 steps to being a great guest (with any kind of host)</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/posts/greatguest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:48:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/posts/greatguest/</guid>
      <description>After many years of moving or traveling a lot and being content with a laptop, a candle and a place to sleep, I got a place where I could host people. And through that experience of hosting a lot of people, friends, friends of friends, parents, and more, I realized that my view on being a good guest was maybe not everybody&amp;rsquo;s.
Once upon a time a new friend stayed with me for a few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clearing Call</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/posts/clearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/posts/clearing/</guid>
      <description>Clearing Talk To engage in a clearing conversation that allows us speak plainly to each other and understand each other’s stories, feelings and desires If we have time / get to a point that we are ready to move on, we can move to actionable next steps on how to work better together going forward
Please share with the other person in advance, an email or document with 1 (max 2) situations following the clearing framework (see below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditación en la impermanencia</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/meditacion-en-la-impermanencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/meditacion-en-la-impermanencia/</guid>
      <description>Guide to emoji usage in Hugo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditación en la incertidumbre del momento de la muerte </title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/meditaci%C3%B3n-en-la-incertidumbre-del-momento-de-la-muerte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/meditaci%C3%B3n-en-la-incertidumbre-del-momento-de-la-muerte/</guid>
      <description>V. Sangye Khadro
Esta es una meditación en la llamada primera raíz, punto principal de la meditación sobre la muerte en nueve puntos. A saber: la muerte es inevitable e ineludible. Los otros dos puntos raíz (que se trataran en otras meditaciones) son: el momento de la muerte es desconocido, y sólo la práctica espiritual es de ayuda en dicho momento. Preparación Nos sentamos con una postura cómoda, la espalda recta y el cuerpo relajado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditación en la inevitabilidad de la muerte</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/meditaci%C3%B3n-en-la-inevitabilidad-de-la-muerte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/meditaci%C3%B3n-en-la-inevitabilidad-de-la-muerte/</guid>
      <description>V. Sangye Khadro
Escucha esta meditacion aca Esta es una meditación en la llamada primera raíz, punto principal de la meditación sobre la muerte en nueve puntos. A saber: la muerte es inevitable e ineludible. Los otros dos puntos raíz (que se trataran en otras meditaciones) son: el momento de la muerte es desconocido, y sólo la práctica espiritual es de ayuda en dicho momento.
Preparación Nos sentamos con una postura cómoda, la espalda recta y el cuerpo relajado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal - Curriculum Vitae EN</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/cven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/cven/</guid>
      <description>Berlin / Bogota ● +4915739625098 ● www.yatan.co ● me@yatan.co
Summary Yatan Blumenthal is an international professional with 10+ years experience in project management, sales, team building, community building, technology building, research and training and coaching. Trained as mindfulness &amp;amp; emotional intelligence teacher for work he always enjoys building great teams with a great culture. Also trained as a full stack web developer, he is very comfortable in working in tech focused teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal - Hoja De Vida</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/cves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/cves/</guid>
      <description>me@yatan.co ● +4915739625098 ● www.yatan.co
Resumen Yatan Blumenthal Vargas es un profesional con experiencia en management, manejo de projectos, coaching, technology building y emprendimiento creativo. Es certificado como un entrenador de inteligencia emocional Search Inside Yourself y tambien desarrollador de software. Ha trabajado armando programas de educacion y manejando proyectos con corporates, startups y ONGs en Asia, America Latina y Europa.
Educación Profesional 05/2018-05/2019 | Search Inside Yourself Certified Teacher; Entrenador en mindfulness z Inteligencia Emocional con enfoque en liderazgo y excelencia de trabajo de equipos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I am Yatan I like to build and I like to help.
Highly curious about teams, technology and business I have built many accelerator programs, venture builders and companies for Fortune 500 Companies, Government Agencies, NGOs and Startups.
I also help teams and organizations become more human and better performing through authenticity, mindfulness and emotional intelligence.
Book a call
Mindful and Authentic Leadership Training
I am passionate about helping people get the best out of themselves and their team, there is no time to waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book a call with Yatan</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/cal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/cal/</guid>
      <description> Schedule time with me </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Inside Yourself (SIY)</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/search-inside-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/search-inside-yourself/</guid>
      <description>The Program Search Inside Yourself - Leadership Training Originally developed at Google, Search Inside Yourself teaches practical mindfulness, emotional intelligence and leadership tools to unlock your full potential at work and in life. Bring Search Inside Yourself to your organization Program Overview
Search Inside Yourself takes an evidence-based approach combining neuroscience, attention-training and emotional intelligence. The program provides practical tools that can be applied immediately in life or at work. We start with a foundation of mindfulness, and build the core emotional intelligence domains that lead to outstanding leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un curso de milagros libro de ejercicios</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/acimworkbook.es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/acimworkbook.es/</guid>
      <description>LIBRO DE EJERCICIOS PRIMERA PARTE Introducción 1. Para que los ejercicios de este libro de ejercicios tengan sentido para ti, es necesario, como marco de referencia, disponer de una base teórica como la que provee el texto. Es la práctica de los ejercicios, no obstante, lo que te permitirá alcanzar el objetivo del curso. Una mente sin entrenar no puede lograr nada. El propósito de este libro de ejercicios es entrenar a tu mente a pensar según las líneas expuestas en el texto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un curso de milagros</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/uncursodemilagros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/uncursodemilagros/</guid>
      <description>Edición de 2016-07-01
PREFACIO Este Prefacio se escribió en 1977 como respuesta a las muchas solicitudes recibidas para que se incluyera una introducción a Un curso de milagros. Las primeras dos partes de este Prefacio, ¿Cómo se originó? y ¿Qué es? las escribió la misma Helen Schucman; la última parte fue escrita mediante el proceso de dictado interno descrito más adelante.
¿Cómo se originó? Un curso de milagros dio comienzo con la súbita decisión de dos personas de colaborar en el logro de un objetivo común.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Course in Miracles: Original Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/acim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yatan.co/meditation/acim/</guid>
      <description>A Course in Miracles is spiritual guide for life. The book begins: This is A Course in Miracles, it is a required course. Only the time you take it is voluntary.The Course as the book is commonly known, comprises of 365 lessons of spiritual guidance. It is divided into three sections: Text, Workbook for Students, and Manual for Teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
